“The atmosphere calmed down so quickly,” Alma chuckled.

“Indeed it did.” Sara sighed tiredly.

“Hehe,” Orphia giggled.

“I don’t want to say anything arrogant, so I won’t. However, once everything’s over, I will return to this house. Until then, can I leave this place to you? While I hope nothing will happen, it’s possible that something may occur to this house or Rodania while I’m away. If an emergency arises, I hope you can all support Aishia.”

“Of course.”

“Thank you. I appreciate it,” Rio replied.

“There’s nothing to thank us for.”

“Yup.”

“Indeed.”

Sara, Orphia, and Alma chimed in.

“No, there are so many things I have to thank you all for.”

“Really? I can’t seem to think of any reason why we need to be thanked...” The girls exchanged curious looks.

“Part of the reason why I decided against disappearing from you all was also because of Sara, Orphia, Alma, and Latifa. That’s why.”

“Well, we don’t remember doing anything.”

Sara and the others still looked curious.

“That’s not true. You’re waiting for someone like me to return. You’re telling me that it’s okay for me to return. I still have my doubts about whether it’s truly okay for me to come back, but I’m really happy because of that,” Rio said quietly. That’s why he thought it would be okay to change.

Sara, Orphia, and Alma suddenly looked embarrassed. Latifa was grinning from ear to ear, while Miharu watched them all with a pleasant smile.

“Th-There’s no need to thank us for something that’s only natural.” Sara made eye contact with Rio, then averted her gaze with an unsteady voice.

“Ah, Sara’s being shy,” Orphia pointed out in amusement.

“I-I’m not being shy,” Sara turned away and denied.

Alma joined the teasing after seeing that, and the others all smiled in amusement. Rio smiled too.

This occurred one week before Rio snuck into the Proxia Castle. It was a peaceful moment of time, like the calm before a storm.

Bonus Short Stories

Rio’s Sleeping Face

One day, sometime before departing for the Proxia Empire, Rio visited the stone house by himself; Celia and Aishia had remained in Rodania. Since the meal with Liselotte was planned for tomorrow, he informed the residents of the house he wouldn’t be returning to Rodania that night.

“Does that mean you’re staying the night, Onii-chan?!” Latifa asked happily. She had secured a seat beside Rio in the living room.

“Yeah, that’s the plan.”

“Yay!” Latifa clung to Rio with a cheer.

“That hurts, Latifa,” Rio said with a pained expression.

“That means we’ll have to have a feast tonight,” Orphia said with a smile.

Latifa immediately endorsed the idea. “Agreed! I’ll help too!”

The other girls also offered to help with the cooking. “I’ll help make something too,” Rio added.

“You’re finally back, so you should just rest. We’ll do the cooking tonight,” Sara said to him.

Alma nodded. “That’s right. Though, it’s still a little early for dinner.”

“You should take a bath and relax,” Miharu said, encouraging Rio to make himself at home.

“All right... I’ll take you up on that offer.”

And so, it was decided that everyone would make dinner for Rio. He took a bath in the stone house for the first time in a while to relieve his fatigue, then returned to the living room with damp hair. It seemed like the girls had begun cooking in the kitchen, as he could hear them chatting to each other harmoniously.

It’s kind of hard to relax while leaving all the housework to everyone... Rio thought while sitting in the living room. He split the housework evenly with Celia in Rodania, but even then he was always cleaning things up in advance, so having such idle time was a new feeling.

Maybe I should read a book.

With that decided, Rio stood up and headed to the bookshelf in the living room, picking out a random book and returning to the sofa.

While listening to the lively voices of the girls, he opened the book and silently moved his eyes over the pages. However, the bath must have warmed his body and made him feel sleepy, as he started dozing off. Several minutes later, his eyes were closed as he’d fallen asleep on the sofa.

Some time passed. “Zzz...” Rio breathed quietly in his sleep.

“Haruto...?” Miharu appeared in the living room, noticing Rio asleep on the sofa. She walked up to him and called his name, confirming there was no response, before bringing a throw blanket from another room and gently covering Rio’s body with it.

“Hehe.” Miharu smiled happily at Rio’s innocent face; she’d wake him when it was closer to dinnertime. She was about to return to the kitchen with that thought, but she was reluctant to leave the precious sight of Rio’s sleeping face behind and kept watching.

However, she couldn’t delay her return forever, so with an iron will, she turned to go back to the kitchen, when—

“La—?!”

Before she knew it, Latifa was standing behind her, covering Miharu’s mouth.

“Shh! You’ll scare Onii-chan if you scream,” she whispered, sitting beside Rio and clinging to him as if it were the most natural thing in the world.

“Wh-What are you doing, Latifa?” Miharu asked, blinking.

“You looked like you wanted to be spoiled by Onii-chan, so I’m showing you an example of how to do it.”

“I-I wasn’t thinking that,” Miharu denied in a flustered whisper.

“Mm... Latifa?” Rio naturally woke up from the noise and noticed Latifa sitting beside him.

“Yup. I’ll wake you up when it’s time to eat, so you can keep sleeping.”

“Okay.” Rio fell back asleep without noticing Miharu, probably because he was used to Latifa clinging to him, or perhaps because he had his guard down.

After that, Latifa had her fill of clinging to Rio until she was satisfied. “And this is how you act spoiled around Onii-chan,” she said to Miharu smugly, standing up without a sound.

“You’re the only one who can do that, Latifa...” Miharu’s reply was slightly exasperated and a bit envious.

Professor Celia’s Wardrobe

Before Rio departed for the Proxia Empire, in the estate that Rio received from the Restoration in Rodania...

One morning, Celia was in her underwear, glaring at the clothes spread out on her bed. They were all casual clothes she’d bought at a branch store of the Ricca Guild, and every piece was cute in design.

“Hmm, I wonder what I should wear?” Celia muttered in thought, trying to decide her outfit for the day.

“Celia.” Aishia suddenly materialized in the room; she had been sleeping in Celia’s room in spirit form last night. She appeared while yawning sleepily, as though she had just woken up.

“Oh! Good morning, Aishia.” Celia was in her underwear, but she seemed totally used to the situation.

“Morning. Are you choosing your clothes?”

“Yup. I can’t decide which would be best to wear while I’m out shopping today. I know—could you give me your opinion on which outfit I should wear?”

“You bought everything here with Haruto, so I’m sure he’ll be happy with whatever you choose,” Aishia said, making a precise guess of Celia’s requirements.

“I-I never said I was choosing for Rio’s sake!” Celia denied with a flushed face. She then continued speaking in a whisper. “B-But... I’ll be going out with Rio, and while we’re together he’ll have to look at me, so it wouldn’t hurt to wear something that suits Rio’s tastes.”

“Do you want to ask Haruto, then?”

“I-It’s fine. I’m sure he has his own preparations to make.”

“You don’t have to call him here. I can telepathically share what I see and hear with Haruto over short distances.”

“You can do that?” The possibilities were so unlimited with spirit arts, they surprised Celia even to this day.

“Yup. It’s only possible between a spirit and contract holder with a path connected.”

“How convenient!”

“It has more limitations than just telepathically speaking, but I should be able to show you to Haruto from this distance,” Aishia said, staring at Celia intently.

“I see... Then maybe I’ll take you up on that offer... Wait, I’m in my underwear! S-Stop! Don’t do it! You’re not showing Haruto what I look like right now, are you?!”

It was an eventful morning for Celia.

Elemental ☆ Summer Festival!

On this summer day, Amakawa Haruto was going to the Tanabata festival with his friends. He set off for their meetup spot near the festival location when the sky started to dim.

“Amakawa-senpai,” a cute voice called out. Haruto turned in the direction of the voice.

“Rikka-chan.”

It was Minamoto Rikka, his junior from middle school. Her long hair she normally had down was tied up in a short style, and she was seated on a bench wearing a white, flower-patterned yukata. In her hand was an uchiwa fan that must have been handed out on the streets near the festival; she used it to fan a cool breeze.

“Good evening, Amakawa-senpai,” Rikka greeted Haruto in a bright voice.

“Good evening, Rikka-chan. You came in your yukata.”

“Yup. Does it look good?”

“Yes, very. You give off a different feeling with your hair tied up—I was captivated.”

“Thank you,” Rikka said with a bashful smile.

“Is anyone else here yet?” Haruto looked around.

“Nope. No one else is here yet, so I’m the first to arrive. That makes you the second, Amakawa-senpai. Here, have a seat.” Rikka gestured at the empty space on the bench beside her.

“If you don’t mind, then.” Haruto sat down right next to Rikka.

“I’m glad it was sunny today.”

“Yeah. It was kind of hot, though.” Haruto noted that he was sweating even though he had only walked a short distance.

“Then I’ll share the cool breeze with you.” Rikka fanned the uchiwa in her hand in Haruto’s direction.

“Thanks. It feels nice,” Haruto said with a smile. He casually looked around and noticed a stall selling drinks. “Say, Rikka-chan. Do you like ramune?” he asked.

“Huh? Yeah,” Rikka nodded.

“Wait here, then,” Haruto said, standing up and heading towards the stall. He handed the stall owner some change and received a ramune bottle and two paper cups before coming back.

“One bottle’s a little too much for one person, so will you drink it with me? It’s also my thank-you for fanning me,” he said, handing Rikka a paper cup.

“Thank you very much. I’d love to,” Rikka giggled, accepting the cup.

“Here you go.” Haruto first poured the ramune into Rikka’s cup.

“I’ll pour it for you as well, Amakawa-senpai.” Rikka put her cup and uchiwa down on the bench and took the bottle from Haruto, pouring the drink into his paper cup.

“Thanks.”

“Ramune’s nice, but I don’t really get a chance to drink it outside of festivals. When I was a child, I drank it every time I went to a festival.” Those words appeared to be the truth, as Rikka poured the drink smoothly while keeping the marble characteristic to ramune drinks held in the cavity of the bottle.

“I didn’t really play with them, but I remember taking the marble out of the drinks afterwards and saving them.”

“I can relate. I also have all the marbles from my childhood saved in a drawer at home.”

“I think mine are still at home too. All right, let’s have some.”

“Thanks for the drink. Mm, sure brings back memories.” Rikka peered inside her cup and smiled happily, then took a sip of the drink.

“Hah... I’ve been brought back to life.” Haruto gulped down his ramune and sighed.

“Yeah, it’s so good,” Rikka said, entranced. “I’ll keep fanning you as thanks for the ramune, senpai.” She resumed fanning a cool breeze towards Haruto with her uchiwa.

“I’ll be off now,” Aishia said once Orphia caught Celia, who was still in a fluster. Aishia accelerated upwards once again, flying after Reiss.

It doesn’t look like she’ll be giving up. Honestly, what an unlucky day. Reiss had a rare look of pain on his face. Just how did things end up like this? He recalled the events leading up to this moment...

◇　◇　◇

Shortly before Rio left for the Proxia Empire...

On the upper balcony of the Proxia Castle stood Lucius, Emperor Nidoll, and Ambassador Reiss. Lucius had barged in on them.

“The bastard is my prey,” he said about Rio, then left, leaving Nidoll and Reiss behind on the balcony.

“Now...shall I explain the plan to kill Haruto Amakawa—the boy also known as Rio and the Black Knight?” Reiss brought up cheerfully.

“You’re killing him? Was the brat not capable of reaching the transcendent ones?” Nidoll asked frankly.

“Well, part of the reason why the transcendent ones were brought up as an example was to control Lucius. Though it seems it had no effect at all.” Reiss shrugged in annoyance. “However, it’s true that the Black Knight’s combat power exceeds those of the great hero class from the time of the Divine War. While I don’t know if he’s capable of wide-ranged attacks like the awakened heroes, it would be wise to consider his individual combat ability just as threatening as theirs. He does have a contract with a humanoid spirit, after all. Their threat when combined would be...”

“Something that would surpass an awakened hero?” Nidoll’s expression twisted with a grin.

“You seem rather pleased. This isn’t good news for me, though.” Reiss sighed wearily.

I’m sure their combined power cannot reach that of the transcendent ones, but the fact they’re equal to the awakened heroes means they’ll be equal to us when unbound... Which would be extremely problematic if true, Reiss thought.

“And so you plan on splitting them up and crushing them individually. Indeed, that is one of the fundamentals of war.” Nidoll correctly guessed the general plan Reiss was thinking of.

“Yes. He should be utterly convinced that Lucius is connected to me, being that I am the ambassador of the Proxia Empire. If his resentment for Lucius is strong, he shouldn’t be able to overlook this country. It won’t be long before he comes here—to this very castle. We should use that chance carefully.”

“And that is when you want me to pass a message on to the Black Knight?”

Reiss nodded in satisfaction. “I’m glad you’re quick on the uptake. However, his arrival will be unpredictable, and if he comes across Lucius, we’ll end up involved in a destructive head-on collision between them. This situation will need to be avoided.”

“That seems interesting as well.”

“It’s not interesting for me. That is why there will be a need to prepare a different location for the showdown and make Lucius avoid the castle for the time being. I shall take on that role myself.”

“In which case, my role will be to guide the Black Knight.”

“Indeed. If his target is merely Lucius, then he wouldn’t want to fight more people for no reason. Use that to your advantage and have him follow Lucius.”

“Will it really go that smoothly?”

“That will depend on your capabilities, and a little bit of luck. If he decides that this castle isn’t worth his time for a visit, then the plan would be ruined.”

“It would.”

“However, in that case, we can just guide him in another way to the battlefield I shall prepare. But I do believe he will stop by this castle. Not even he should be able to slip past the castle’s barrier undetected, so it’ll be your time to shine once he’s snuck in.”

“Naturally, I should treat him as an intruder. Is that correct?” Nidoll asked with a slight bounce to his voice.

“As long as you guide him to the location of the battlefield, I leave the rest to you. However, you absolutely must clarify that your relationship with Lucius is as mercenary and employer, and you must hint that Lucius is in the Paladia Kingdom. That is what I request of you.”

“The battlefield shall be Paladia, you say. It is a shame I cannot go there myself... I will have to make do with enjoying the opening act. It has been some time since I last faced a powerful opponent. It makes my heart leap.” Nidoll spoke brightly as he imagined his confrontation with Rio here.

“Keep things in moderation... Even if he does sneak in, he won’t fight with the intent to kill, as his goal is to obtain information. If the battle gets too heated and intense, the worst may come to pass.” Reiss narrowed his eyes as he emphasized his point.

“Surely that mustn’t be the sound of concern for my defeat that I am hearing. And from you, no less.”

“If it comes down to an all-out battle, then even you will be in an unfavorable position in your current state. It may not be what you want to hear, but have some restraint in your fun.”

“Fine.”

“Good. During that time, I’ll drag Lucius around and work on securing our victory.”

“What do you intend on doing?” Nidoll asked in interest.

“My first idea is to bring at least one of the heroes onto our side as a pawn. At worst, we can stimulate their awakening and throw them against the Black Knight.”

“Hmm. Speaking of heroes, there was a report that a certain church has made a move.”

“You mean the saint of the Church of the End? I was planning on leaving that case until after the Black Knight had been dealt with. In terms of a threat, he is far above them.”

“Which hero do you intend on luring to this side, then?”

“There’s one hero without any affiliation to a kingdom or organization, masquerading as an adventurer. There’s been various activity around the Rubia Kingdom’s princess regarding that, so I am considering using this opportunity to take the hero in. If things go according to plan, this should act as a distraction for Lucius as well.”

“How overly protective of you.”

“There is no better candidate at present than Lucius, after all... I’d like to avoid losing him at all costs. That is why I’m bending over backwards trying to keep him pleased.” Reiss shook his head tiredly, while Nidoll smirked in agreement.

“I’m sure it’s beyond my imagination. So, what will be the core of your plan for victory over the Black Knight?”

“It’s simple. We just have to take hostages. Rio may be strong, but he’s susceptible to what will happen if we take hostages. It’ll merely be a matter of taking someone precious to him from his home base while he’s away. We’ll be making a total enemy of him if we mess up, but, well... This method will suit Lucius’s tastes much more, so it will be easier to gain his cooperation,” Reiss said with a cold laugh. Defeating an enemy by aiming for their weakness was a normal tactic in battle.

“I see,” Nidoll hummed with meaning.

“Does something worry you?”

“You are indeed a cunning man. You excel in making people do things for you. However, perhaps there’s something that you’re forgetting?”

“Which would be...?”

“That Lucius is also a cunning beast. He moves on instinct, preying on others. He isn’t of the caliber to be kept as a pet.”

“I do believe I am aware.”

“I don’t know how you’ve calculated your victory, but... No matter how much Lucius is forced into working with you in order to locate the Black Knight, as long as you hide the important things from him, he won’t obey you,” Nidoll warned.

“Fine. I shall find the occasion to tell him everything other than the fact his beloved boy is coming to the castle,” Reiss said, raising both shoulders.

“I see. I’ve given my warning.”

“Indeed. Now, it’s about time I take my leave.”

With the essential matters discussed, Reiss turned his back to Nidoll and walked off.

“Now, what to do from here...” Nidoll’s muttering was delightfully animated.

“Hmm? Did you say something?”

“I-I surr—aaah...!”

The weight on his back increased, making Renji scream. Just then, several bolts of light came flying straight towards Lucius from his front side. Each bolt was aimed accurately to pierce through Lucius’s body.

The bolts of light originated from Sylvie, who stood in a posture as though she had just drawn and thrust her rapier-shaped enchanted sword.

“Huh?” Lucius swung the sword in his left hand. Immediately, darkness swelled and swallowed up the bolts of light. Sylvie started charging towards Lucius, thrusting into empty space from several meters away. Each thrust released several bolts of light from the end of her rapier, every bolt aimed to snipe at Lucius’s torso with precision.

“Ha!” Lucius sneered, dealing with Sylvie’s bolts head-on. He swung his sword lightly, releasing a darkness that swallowed the light beams. Despite that, Sylvie continued firing the light from her enchanted sword. Then, once the distance between them had reduced to roughly ten meters—

“Here, let me return them,” Lucius said, pointing his sword at Sylvie.

“Huh?!”

The same attack that Sylvie had fired came flying at her from every direction. Her speed dropped from her continuous charge. She tried to change directions quickly, but the light flew at where she was trying to evade towards. When she tried to find another escape route, she realized for the first time that the bolts were coming from every direction. Because of that, Sylvie’s reaction was delayed.

“Ngh...”

She tried to evade the light bolts in order to minimize the damage as much as possible. However, before Sylvie knew it, she was standing away from the siege of light bolts.

“Wha...?”

Just how did she move instantaneously? Sylvie was speechless. Then, Reiss stepped beside her.

“Your jokes have gone too far. Are you trying to kill Princess Sylvie?” Reiss asked Lucius in a fed-up tone.

“Don’t get in the way. You let that woman pass you on purpose,” Lucius pointed out with a snort.

“That’s because you were hurting him a little too much. Well, the match will count as Renji the Aloof’s defeat due to Princess Sylvie’s intervention anyway,” Reiss said, looking down at Renji on the ground.

“Ah... Aah...” Renji was barely conscious, groaning with his eyes open slightly.

“R-Renji! Ngh...” Sylvie snapped back to her senses and ran up to Renji. His physical body had been strengthened during the fight, but it was hard to imagine he could maintain that while unconscious.

The damage to his body and the amount of blood lost appeared to be so severe, there seemed to be no way for him to survive. Sylvie shook at the tragic state of Renji’s body and glared at Lucius.

“Hey, it was a consensual match. I don’t think I deserve to be glared at for that. He never said he surrendered either, y’know?”

It wasn’t that Renji didn’t say it, but that he couldn’t. Lucius looked down at Renji and chuckled smugly.

“The match was settled the moment you cut his arm and legs off! You were fully intending on killing him!”

“That goes for the both of us, though. He tried to kill me with no hesitation from the very first blow.”

“Guh...”

Indeed, since Renji had tried to finish the match in the first blow by killing Lucius, Sylvie couldn’t argue any further.

“The two of you can leave your argument at that. He won’t die like this—or rather, I won’t let him die like this.” Reiss had picked up Renji’s severed limbs while the two of them argued harshly.

“He won’t die...?” Sylvie looked at the severed limbs in anger.

“Yes. Because he’s a hero.”

“Wha...” Sylvie was shocked into speechlessness by Reiss’s words.

Why...does he know...? Renji’s mind thought in a daze. However, with that question as a final thought, his consciousness faded.

“Falling unconscious from this... It’s proof of how he’s still unawakened as a hero, I suppose. It seems he’s still inexperienced,” Reiss said, holding the severed limbs to their original positions. Renji’s limbs began visibly reattaching themselves as though they were being drawn together.

“Wh...?!” Sylvie swallowed her breath in shock.

“See? He won’t die.” Reiss smiled as though he knew everything from the start. Well, he’s still unawakened as a hero, so his recovery speed is rather slow... And as a human, he’s still bound by his human emotions.

“Wh-What is the meaning of this?! What?! Reiss! You knew Renji was a hero from the beginning, didn’t you?!” Sylvie ranted in confusion.

“You were somewhat aware of the Aloof’s identity yourself, no? And it was because you saw the heroes at the banquet in the Galarc Kingdom too, I’d wager?”

“...What do you intend on doing with Renji?” Sylvie asked with a disgusted look. Seeing how calm Reiss was helped her regain her composure a little.

“As agreed, he’ll become my subordinate.”

“You’ll make a hero your subordinate?”

“Do you find that disrespectful? Just so you know, I value him for his latent combat potential rather than his political use. We can never have enough superior fighters, after all,” Reiss replied to Sylvie’s frown with a creepy smile.

“...” Sylvie fell silent.

“You don’t have to be so wary—I won’t turn his power towards you. As long as we are allied, that is.” In other words, it would be a different story if they were enemies.

“Now, shall we go? Princess Estelle will continue her stay with us, but as a sign of our trust, you may look after your friend for the time being. Please explain his position to him clearly.” Leaving behind those words, Reiss walked away. Lucius, who had completely lost interest in Renji, followed him.

Renji’s severed limbs had been reattached and the bleeding had stopped.

Renji...

Sylvie picked up the unconscious young man with a miserable expression and followed behind Reiss and the others.

◇　◇　◇

That night, Lucius and Reiss returned to Proxia Castle with Second Princess Estelle. Renji, who was still unconscious, was taken to the royal castle by Princess Sylvie.

Lucius locked himself in his room and sat by the window to glare at a few documents. These were reports regarding Rio which Reiss had handed to him to read while he went to speak with Nidoll. Lucius reread the reports over and over again to search for information he could use.

“Sorry to keep you waiting.”

Reiss had settled his matters with Nidoll and arrived at Lucius’s room. He came to a stop as soon as he entered the room and spotted Lucius seated by the window.

“Someone in the castle used a teleport crystal,” Lucius said without taking his eyes off the reports. A short time ago he had detected the scattered ode and mana characteristic of space sorcery.

“Impressive. Arein, Lucci, and Ven just left for a job. I had them head to Rodania in the Beltrum Kingdom.”

Lucius lifted his head for the first time and glared at Reiss sharply. “What are you scheming now?”

“It seems you still don’t trust me. There was no scheming—I sent the three of them to search for the location of your fated partner, the Black Knight. I’ve handed you the reports with all the information concerning him, sending off my subordinates using precious teleport crystals that cannot be mass-produced just to gather information. It’s about time you trusted me a little.”

“That depends on what you say next. You said you’d set up the stage for me to fight that Rio bastard alone if I went with you to the Rubia Kingdom, right?”

“Indeed, I have no intention of breaking that promise.” Reiss nodded without hesitation.

“But you interfered with the end of my fight with that brat today.” Lucius recalled the moment when Princess Sylvie had intervened.

“The one who interfered was Princess Sylvie and not myself.”

“Don’t dodge the point. You would have been able to stop that woman.”

“I do not deny that. However, I did inform you before we entered that kingdom that I would intervene if you went too far. I allowed Princess Sylvie to act because your careless actions could have cornered the hero to the point of awakening.”

“...What do you intend on doing during my fight with Rio, then? Even if you prepare a stage for me to fight the bastard, will you interfere while I’m in the middle of fighting him?” Even if Reiss himself didn’t interfere in the fight, he could easily allow someone else to do so like he had done with Sylvie. Lucius was wary of that.

“As I said before, I will prepare a stage for you where no one can interfere at all.”

“But you believe I’ll lose if I have a rematch with him.” That was what Lucius was most displeased with. It was also the basis of his suspicion that Reiss would interfere.

“...I admit, I believe you’re at a disadvantage. However, as long as he is human, he should have as many openings as you need. I believe I stated this—if you assist me in my business at the Rubia Kingdom, I will explain my entire plan to you. I mentioned it before you fought Renji as well, but I’m sure it’ll be to your liking.”

“Then let’s hear it.”

“Of course.”

“But first, I want to confirm something.”

“Whatever you wish,” Reiss nodded with a shrug.

“You already know Rio’s location, don’t you?” Lucius asked, getting straight to the point.

“No, I’m afraid I don’t know his precise location... He’s able to fly about the sky freely, as you know. He also moves at an extraordinary speed,” Reiss said without batting an eye, his explanation the same as it had always been.

“So you don’t know the bastard’s location, but you say you can set the stage for a battle for me. If you end up saying anything wrong, I’ll be acting by myself. I won’t go along with your stalling any longer,” Lucius said threateningly.

“I understand. However, I’d like you to listen to my explanation of why this time spent waiting isn’t a waste. If you can understand my reasoning, I hope you will be willing to wait until the right moment arrives. If you’re insistent on rushing towards your death, then I will cancel the arrangements myself.” Reiss sounded oddly serious for once.

The two of them stared at each other.

“...Fine,” Lucius nodded without breaking eye contact.

“Then, for my explanation: as insurance for the worst-case scenario, I’m thinking of kidnapping the people close to the Black Knight. Once I’ve secured that insurance, I can promise not to lay a finger on your fight with him,” Reiss explained.

“I see. They might know where Rio is too. It’s not a bad idea.” Of course, Lucius had also considered obtaining a hostage.

“However, it’s easier said than done. There is one problem with this plan.”

“No doubt.” Lucius’s reply was immediate. He knew Reiss wasn’t foolish enough to pass on an opportunity with guaranteed success. In this regard, he trusted him completely.

“I’ve identified several candidates that could be secured as hostages and located them. As you may have seen in the documents on the Black Knight, the candidates are either powerful themselves, or have powerful people around them... It’s been a challenge to find an easy mark to grab. If I slip up, I’ll be making an enemy out of him in the future, so the only time I can act is when I’m certain of my success. That is why I’d like your cooperation in securing the hostages,” Reiss said with a dramatic sigh.

“...Who’s the target?”

“The first candidate is Celia Claire. As you know, she was his former teacher at the Beltrum Academy back when he was attending. She’s currently affiliated with the Restoration in Rodania. That being said, I cannot imagine the Black Knight would leave her completely defenseless, so there’s a high possibility his contract spirit is acting as her guard... Even then, she would probably be the best target.”

“For what reason? Doesn’t his contract spirit have a fair amount of hidden strength?”

“The reason is plain and simple—helpless women make the best hostages, no? And no matter how strong that humanoid spirit is, there’s a limit to what can be handled alone. There are plenty of ways to deal with a spirit burdened by a hindrance.”

“...I see.” Though faint, Lucius showed a pleased smile for the first time at that.

“His contract spirit is menacing, but as long as nothing else gets in the way, the two of us should be able to get it done; we should be able to kidnap Celia. She would also make a good political bargaining chip in the future,” Reiss said with a twisted grin.

“Ha, you’re one greedy bastard yourself,” Lucius sneered, seeing through him.

“If I didn’t gain something as well, you wouldn’t believe me anyway,” Reiss said, understanding Lucius well.

“Well, yeah...”

“How about it? I’ll apologize for putting on airs over such a straightforward means, but I believe hostages are a method you also enjoy using. As long as there’s a hostage, there will be no need to fear my interference. It’s not a bad idea—in fact, I believe it’s a most reasonable suggestion...”

“...Fine. We’ll take a hostage.” Though he had a hint of displeasure on his face, Lucius nodded.

“Excellent.” The corners of Reiss’s mouth lifted upwards.

“Hmph. When do you plan on going through with this?” Lucius snorted and asked.

“It’s short notice, but in two days’ time. That’s why I sent Arein and the others off in advance. They are to spend one day gathering information about Celia Claire, and if the situation looks favorable, then we’ll go ahead with the plan.”

“Sounds like everything’s been planned from start to finish. Exactly how you want it.” Lucius’s frown spoke of his discontent towards that.

“You’re overestimating me there. I’ve had consecutive miscalculations in regards to the Black Knight, after all. Why, a new miscalculation occurred right when we were absent from the castle...” Reiss lamented.

“I heard an intruder snuck into the castle last night. And that they fought that Nidoll and escaped,” Lucius suddenly said.

“...Oh? You’re aware of it already. Nidoll said he placed a gag order on the topic, so I was thinking of informing you as a sign of our collaboration.” Reiss’s eyes widened in apparent surprise.

“Don’t play the fool. You predicted Rio would come to this castle too, didn’t you? Even though you said you didn’t know his location just now...” Lucius questioned him with emphasis on his words.

“The former was a miscalculation. He probably took into account my position as the Proxia Empire ambassador and snuck here suspecting my connection to you,” Reiss stated with an indifferent expression.

Lucius knew that Reiss was in regular contact with the imperial capital. He probably received word that Rio had invaded the castle before deciding to return at this point in time.

“...Then what about the latter?”

Figuring he would just be lied to anyway, Lucius didn’t pry any further into the former. He wasn’t satisfied, but it was a better idea to remain silent about that here.

“I didn’t lie to you. At present, I do not know of his precise location. However, thanks to Nidoll’s quick-wittedness on the spur of the moment, I do have an idea of his destination.”

“Where is it?” Lucius questioned immediately with hatred burning in his eyes.

“You don’t have to glare at me with those terrifying eyes—I won’t hide anything at this point. He’s heading for Prince Duran in the Paladia Kingdom, since Nidoll received information that you were working there just recently.”

“Paladia, huh... Not bad. Finally some luck on our side.” Lucius smiled faintly at the lead he finally received on Rio’s whereabouts.

“And so, I’ll be heading to the Paladia Kingdom now to prepare Prince Duran for contact with him. I’ll have Prince Duran guide him towards a specified location, so you should stay here and conserve your energy. I will return soon. If you disappear without notice in the future, I will consider our collaborative partnership terminated, so don’t try anything strange,” Reiss emphasized. He probably had no intention of telling Lucius where specifically in Paladia they would hold their fight, as a matter of insurance.

“Hmph.” Lucius snorted in discontent at being ordered to wait.

“Hastiness will invite mistakes. I’m sure you’re feeling impatient knowing he’s heading for Paladia, but securing the hostages comes first. We need to confirm Celia Claire’s situation in Rodania and the presence of the humanoid spirit, so wait one more day. I would have preferred to spend several days observing her, so I’ve brought things forward for your sake already,” Reiss said with a sigh, sensing Lucius’s displeasure.

“Get out of my sight and go where you should be going,” Lucius spat with venom. He waved his hand as though he were shooing away an irritating bug.

“Understood.” Reiss gave a troubled shrug and turned around, leaving through the door.

“Arrogant bastard... You don’t know anything,” Lucius muttered to himself in the empty room, standing up to open the door leading to his bedroom. He then called out to the three men waiting inside. “Hey. Arein, Lucci, Ven.”

The three people Reiss thought he had sent to Rodania were here. They were technically Lucius’s subordinates in the Heavenly Lions, but were presently being lent to Reiss as agents of the Proxia Empire.

“I was so anxious Reiss would notice. That was bad for my heart,” Arein said with a strained smile, exuding a cold sweat.

“Not even Reiss would realize the coordinates of the teleport crystals you used led to my room. Using them from his stock was the right move,” Lucius chuckled. Since a magic artifact was required to set the destination coordinates on teleport crystals, crystals and artifacts needed to come in a set.

On top of that, there were also magic artifacts that created barriers preventing the detection of ode and mana fluctuation from teleportation. Lucius used such an artifact to invite Arein and the others to his room without Reiss’s notice.

“But our remaining stock is really low now. Reiss has been carefully managing the teleport crystals and coordinate artifacts,” said Ven.

“Tell me how many you have left, including the ones we pilfered,” Lucius ordered, taking a Strahl region map from his shelf and spreading it open on his bed.

“One teleport crystal Reiss gave us to go to Rodania just now. One that leads to the Galarc Kingdom’s capital. One to a forest in the east of Beltrum where we hid to gather information. Then there’s seven sets of free teleport crystals we’ve pocketed from our missions until now.” Ven took out small pouches of teleport crystals from his breast pocket, placing each on the map at the destination point labeled on the pouches. He left the seven pouches with the free destination crystals on top of the imperial capital where they currently were.

“...I have two teleport crystals to where I was hiding in the Paladia Kingdom, and one to the royal capital there.”

Lucius took out two pouches of teleport crystals and placed them on the map as well.

“Will you get the jump on Reiss with this, Captain?” Lucci asked.

“I’m considering it. As long as we can secure a different hostage to Reiss in the next day, anything works. The problem is whether there are any women with hostage potential left that he hasn’t set his eyes on...” Lucius said, looking down at the documents regarding Rio. The papers had Rio’s past and human relationships recorded on it, detailing how the former orphan from the slums had obtained new people precious to him and was living happily. It was truly a report that infuriated him the more he read, but that was precisely why he examined it carefully from cover to cover.

The people who were deeply related to Rio were noted down with their names and details, but apart from Celia, none of their locations were known. The next most acquainted people with him were also listed, but their locations were either out of reach of the crystals or too securely guarded within a castle.

Should we grab the hero in the Galarc Castle? But with Reiss’s eyes on me, I can’t leave.

The ones who would actually be doing the abducting were Arein and the others. They were all excellent fighters personally trained by Lucius himself, but there was no guarantee they could successfully sneak into a castle and face a hero on par with Renji at the very least. If they failed, they could risk getting captured themselves.

“...Maybe we could just grab the Beltrum sisters?” Lucius muttered, looking through the documents again. The report noted the relationship between Rio and the royal sisters—that Rio attended the Beltrum Royal Academy years ago, how he was treated there, and so on...

I don’t know about the older one, but the younger one already proved to have hostage value when we fought at Amande.

Lucius looked at the text about Rio and the royal sisters while recalling the Amande battle with a sneer.

Back then, Rio had definitely tried to protect Flora. In other words, even if Rio had an unpleasant past with them, they could still be used as hostages.

Thanks to this left eye, I can move short distances easier than before, but I still can’t underestimate that bastard’s mobility in closing distances at instant speeds. I’ll need to pin him down with hostages to seal his movement. It’ll be fine as long as he has a burden on his side. I’ll show him what it’s like to obtain the power to protect others without being able to use it. That’ll infuriate him.

He was an avenger, yet he surrounded himself with people precious to him. He tried to protect irrelevant strangers. What reason did he have to do that?

Was a human seeking revenge really trying to keep a high sense of ethics at the same time? If someone carrying such impurities really came to kill him, Lucius would laugh. Then, he would be truly pissed off.

That was pure deceit. It was hypocrisy—the work of a fool. Sacrificing yourself to protect the weak was unthinkable. It shouldn’t happen.

There was nothing to gain by keeping up that behavior. There would only be things to lose. Someone born in the slums choosing the path of revenge should know that well, yet Rio was trying to keep up his appearance. That was something extremely displeasing. Revolting, even.

Rio’s face—Rio’s eyes when he appeared at Amande for revenge were unforgettable, even now. That attitude that suppressed hatred in order to remain rational...

You and I are birds of the same feather.

That was why he would expose that filthy character of Rio’s and make him taste despair. On top of that, he’d drag Rio’s half-dead body before his precious people, and steal them from him.

That would be Lucius’s retaliation towards Rio. He’d take hostages in order to trap Rio, but he wouldn’t let anyone else get in the way.

I’ll take a hostage. But I never said I’d do so in collaboration with you, Reiss. I told you that bastard was my prey. I’ll take a hostage out of my own will, but no one said I’d use the hostage you prepared.

There was no beast that hunted prey placed fully prepared before them. At the very least, Lucius wouldn’t accept that. It was a different matter when he moved of his own will, but he couldn’t stand being used by others. The only reason why he had moved according to Reiss’s orders until now was to find Rio’s location.

After that, Lucius spent some time staring at the documents with a serious face. Arein and the others watched on silently.

Once he had organized his thoughts, Lucius opened his mouth and said, “Reiss is heading to Duran in the Paladia Kingdom right now. I can’t move from this castle. In order to get the jump on him, you’ll have to move for me.”

“As you wish,” the three of them nodded with wide grins.

“First, the hostage candidates are the royal sisters of Beltrum. You’ll send them to my hideout in the Paladia Forest. Not even Reiss knows of that precise location—it’ll be perfect for outsmarting him,” Lucius chuckled with contempt. “Ven, you warp to Rodania immediately after this and sniff out where the siblings are by tomorrow evening. Take a free teleport crystal and set the coordinates before returning.”

“Roger that.” Ven picked up the pouch with the crystal that led to Rodania, and one of the free destination crystal pouches.

“So what should Arein and I do?” Lucci asked with an excited grin.

“Once you’ve confirmed Reiss’s return, Lucci will go to the Paladia capital. Buy enough supplies so that the princesses don’t drop dead, then teleport to the woods and stock up the cabin. Make your way back here by tomorrow evening.”

“Got it.”

“Arein, you’ll go with Lucci to the Paladia capital. However, you’ll be moving separately once you get there. Get in touch with the first prince Duran as my messenger—tell him to act like he’s following Reiss’s instructions while actually following mine. Duran will be the messenger that lures the bastard to the forest. Return by tomorrow evening.”

“Understood.”

Lucius fired off his orders one after another. Lucci and Arein each picked up the respective teleport crystals they needed.

“Once you’ve finished up your business, you’ll all go to Rodania together. In order to look like you were following Reiss’s orders, that is. We’ll play whatever follows that by ear, but in two days’ time, I’ll find a moment to dump Reiss and go to Paladia. Before that happens, you guys have to kidnap the princesses and return to Rodania without Reiss’s notice.”

“We just leave the royal sisters in the woods after kidnapping them?” Lucci asked.

“Yes. If I assigned one of you as a guard, Reiss would notice your absence and suspect our movements. With our lack of personnel, I’ll have to be the one to retrieve the princesses after I outsmart him. If Reiss tries to shake you down for answers, pretend you don’t know anything and make it work in my favor. You might even get to see his expression look panicked, you know?”

Lucius wouldn’t be able to see that face. However, just imagining it was enough to send the corners of his mouth upwards cheerily.

“Indeed, you’ve reduced them by quite the number. It seems like aiming for your essence to run dry wasn’t the best plan. Which means I’ll have to face you directly from here on...” Reiss muttered with a sigh, raising his right hand into the air. The skeletons scattered around him turned into a murky black mist, gathering around his body. The mist soon changed shape and enlarged itself.

However, Aishia wasn’t about to watch that happen quietly. She used spirit arts to finish off the remaining monsters that attacked her and launched several light spheres at the black mist. The light spheres all made contact with the mist, but—

He’s absorbing the spell...?

The spell had no impact. Aishia could imagine what was happening. Since magic projectiles wouldn’t work, she tried ice spears—but they were also sucked into the mist without any resistance.

During that time, all the monsters attacking her were eliminated, leaving only the black mist that Reiss was within.

After some time, a humanoid skeleton appeared from within the mist. It had a similar form to the skeleton warriors Reiss had created earlier.

However, its size and sinister aura couldn’t be compared to the earlier skeletons. Its body was bigger than the minotaur, and it was equipped with a giant one-handed sword, a sturdy shield, and armor. It even had wings, implying it could fly through the air. It was truly like a demon or fallen angel had descended.

This is his true form? Aishia tilted her head curiously.

But just as she did, the enormous skeleton knight closed in on her at a speed surpassing the minotaurs, easily swinging the several-meter-long sword.

However, Aishia activated her invisible wall and directly caught the attack. At the same time, she fired a shock wave as a counterattack.

A thundering boom echoed. However, the giant skeleton knight was only knocked back slightly, without being sent flying. It had blocked the shock wave with the shield in its hand.

He’s much sturdier than the others.

In that case, she just needed more firepower. Having determined that in an instant, Aishia fired successful powerful shock waves to execute her plan.

The impact created was visually similar to a sonic boom, the energy gathered together on the skeleton knight releasing at once.

“...” Without even a groan, the shield in the skeleton knight’s hand disintegrated into dust. As proof of the tremendous force, its large body lifted into the air and flew backwards. The skeleton knight flapped its wings in an attempt to soften the landing, but Aishia fired a further shock wave. This time there was no shield to stop her, and the skeleton knight received the damage directly against its body. Cracks appeared across the entire skeleton.

Far above in the skies, one figure watched all of it unfold.

This is the strongest familiar I can create right now. Though it can’t reach the level of the great heroes, it should be able to easily crush several people of the hero class. Even then, the best it can do is buy some time... How truly terrifying, Reiss thought. Well, if she can defeat that and mistakenly assume she’s defeated me, it’d be for the best. I still need to track Lucius’s whereabouts, so I’d better leave before she finds me—otherwise she really will put an end to me. My stock of powerful monsters has been diminished quite a bit too.

A tactical retreat was the smartest option here. Reiss immediately flew away in an embodiment of that idea; his figure was soon hidden by the clouds and no longer visible.

“...”

Meanwhile, the skeleton knight was lying faceup on the ground, silent. Its limbs had been crushed, but it was still struggling to move until Aishia landed on its torso and stomped down.

She landed with such incredible force, the impact completely crushed the bones of its torso. The energy of the impact carried through to the ground, creating a small crater.

Then, the eerie light in the skeleton’s eyes faded. One beat later, the body turned into mist and dispersed. There was no magic gem left behind.

“...Did I defeat him?” Alone in the empty wasteland, Aishia cocked her head.

“His presence is gone. There’s no magic gem either.” He surely had to be defeated. But for some reason, something didn’t feel right—it was almost like it had been too easy. Why was that? Unsure of the reason, she looked around at her surroundings for a while. But the eerie aura was completely gone.

I couldn’t find out who Reiss really was in the end...

If he was going to die this easily, she should have questioned him a bit more, Aishia thought.

There was nothing to be gained today. That’s why she felt like her efforts were in vain.

“Do you even know who you are?”

Aishia suddenly recalled Reiss’s words.

“...I don’t know who I really am,” Aishia muttered with a slightly saddened expression. Why? For some reason, recalling her conversation with Reiss made her heart stir restlessly.

Time to return to Celia and the others.

She wanted to see them immediately. And Rio too... With a final glance around the area, Aishia flew for the stone house.

Chapter 5: Paladia Kingdom Infiltration

Two days ago—the same day Renji battled Lucius...

After fighting Nidoll Proxia, Rio left the imperial castle and immediately returned to the inn. When morning arrived, he checked out like a regular customer and left the imperial capital.

His next destination was the Paladia Kingdom, located to the east of the Proxia Empire. The Paladia Kingdom was one of the small kingdoms north of the Galarc Kingdom that was constantly in conflict with its neighbors over disputed territory.

Considering where and how it was obtained, he had his doubts about his information. But after causing such a commotion in the castle, he couldn’t just sneak back in the next day for more. Information was still information, in the end.

There wasn’t anything particularly strange about Lucius selecting this kingdom for his mercenary activities, so without any other leads, Rio had no choice but to head for the Paladia Kingdom.

According to the emperor, the first prince should know something... The problem is how I should make contact with him, Rio thought while he flew. He would probably be granted an audience if he introduced himself as the honorary knight of Galarc, but with his goal being what it was, he didn’t want to involve his official noble position by going through the formal route.

Which left his only option as infiltration, but—

I’ll probably be able to sneak into the castle, except...

If he was to sneak inside, he’d have to wait for the dead of night, but the private rooms of royalty would probably be heavily guarded. If the prince had a wife and children, he’d probably be sleeping with them, and it wasn’t rare for royalty to sleep in bedrooms without windows in order to prevent intruders.

It was possible to force his way through by making the guards sleep, but recalling the commotion created by his fight with Nidoll made him feel reluctant to do that.

...But this isn’t the time to be thinking that. For now, I’ll sneak in and see how it plays out. I’ll have to wait for a chance to approach him.

With a tentative plan in mind, Rio increased his speed slightly—an unusual sign of how restless he was feeling.

◇　◇　◇

The next afternoon, after a slight delay in locating himself amongst the disorderly, crowded small kingdoms, Rio arrived at Paladia Kingdom’s capital.

So this is the Paladia Kingdom, huh?

Rio looked around at the townscape as he walked. The city was spread along a lake shore and looked plain, but had the bustling activity of a larger kingdom’s suburban city. There were several merchants along the trading area of the city shouting for customers to look at their items.

It’s pretty normal... That was Rio’s first impression of the country.

I’ll stay at an inn like yesterday and wait for sunset, then head to the castle right away.

He came to an abrupt stop and looked up at the castle, located on a small hill beside the lake. With its tall and solid castle walls, it looked more like a fortress than a castle. It was also much more compactly sized than the castles in Beltrum and Galarc, which were larger kingdoms.

The possibility of Lucius being inside the castle right now was enough to send him into a bloodthirsty rage, but he calmed himself with a deep breath and went to prepare an inn.

◇　◇　◇

Once the sun set, the Paladia Castle closed its front gate and prohibited anyone from entering or exiting. However, under the cover of darkness, there was one shadow that easily made its way past the patrolling soldiers and over the castle wall.

Rio was dressed in his black coat, hood over his head and mask over his face.

The security’s pretty tight.

He looked down from the top of the wall and observed the security below. There were torches illuminating every corner of the grounds, with many guards patrolling in extremely strict security.

Let’s try the upper floors for now.

Entry through the ground floor looked rather problematic; the residential area of the royalty was probably on the upper floor anyway. With that thought, Rio decided to enter the building from above. Enhancing his physical abilities, he nimbly ran up the wall of the castle. He then stood on the rooftop of the Paladia Castle. There wasn’t a good foundation to stand on, but he stood steadily as he looked around for an entry point into the castle.

From a defensive perspective, castles were normally made without any windows on the lower floors, but as the Paladia Castle was made more like a fortress, there were no windows that could be entered on the upper floors either. They were all windows so narrow, not even a child could fit through them. While there were larger windows every now and then, they were all locked from the inside.

Not even Rio had lockpicking abilities, so he had no way of opening locked windows other than physically breaking them. But that would leave clear evidence of a break-in, which he wanted to avoid. There would be more ways in if he just looked, anyway.

Seems like I can enter through that watchtower.

Rio identified a watchtower as a point of entry. There were soldiers standing guard in the tower that connected to the building, but it didn’t seem like there were any other entry points, so he didn’t have any other choice.

Rio activated a certain wind spirit art—by permeating his magic essence into the surrounding air, he could create a unique space that couldn’t be visually observed. However, this technique couldn’t erase sounds or the essence being released, so moving quickly or touching things would cause the spell to come apart. He had to proceed with extreme caution.

Rio slowly shuffled along the wall, moving below the watchtower. He then activated an additional spirit art, releasing a soft wind laced with magic essence to probe the inside of the watchtower.

Three, huh? The security really is strict. Are they on some kind of emergency alert?

Three guards stood on watch in the tower. However, Rio hadn’t given up on his break-in. He grabbed a handhold and climbed the wall just enough to peek inside the watchtower.

While the three of them are looking the other way...

Rio swiftly and smoothly descended into the tower. Fearing the space would distort and become noticeable, he canceled his optical disguise for a brief instant. At the exact same moment of his landing, he reactivated the spirit art and disappeared in the blink of an eye—it was a magnificent show of skill.

“Hmm?” The closest soldier reacted with a twitch, having picked up the sound of his landing. Rio crouched down on the spot.

“What’s wrong?” another guard asked curiously.

“No, I just thought I heard a noise... Must have imagined it.”

Since there wasn’t even a shadow to be seen, he dismissed it. After checking there was no one in the watchtower other than themselves, the guards diverted their attention again. Rio cautiously stood up and slowly walked through the watchtower and down the corridor leading to the castle.

Right, time to find the first prince’s room.

Pulling himself together, Rio moved through the shadows before canceling his optical disguise spell.

While he didn’t want to walk around the castle visible to the patrolling guards, there could be sorcerers in the castle sensitive to magic essence, or artifacts and barriers made to detect essence reactions.

That was why it was wiser to avoid walking around with magic essence constantly flowing out. Instead, he’d watch for the presence of others, detecting any suspicious essence reactions, then hiding himself as needed to cleverly avoid the eyes of the security.

As someone who had broken into many royal castles already, Rio was a veteran at this. He knew that intruding like this sometimes needed recklessness, so he stepped forward without hesitation. He descended the staircase leading to the tower and reached the main castle building.

He passed several patrolling guards along the way, but he hid himself in the shadows and against the ceiling to avoid their detection. The floor Rio came out on was the second floor. He started walking around to gain an idea of the castle’s interior and state of security.

While the castle wasn’t as big as those of major kingdoms, the guards didn’t leave any blind spots. However, that made things easier to predict. He memorized the areas with the most soldiers and analyzed the construction of the building to determine where the highest-ranked people would most likely be located.

That seems to be the bedroom of the first prince the emperor of Proxia mentioned.

Rio finally located the room of his target. Hiding in the corner of the corridor, he sounded out the situation. The door to the room was closed, and three knights stood guard in front of it. This made entering rather difficult.

“Hah, I want to go back to my room and sleep. Prince Duran sure has it nice, having fun on the other side of that door.”

He heard one of the knights muttering that.

Since he had learned the first prince’s name was Duran at the inn he was staying at, he knew there was no mistaking that information. Apparently he was very famous throughout the city for being quite the military man.

“Did you see the new woman Prince Duran brought today?”

“Yeah, she was pretty cute for a commoner.”

“Apparently she’s a famous poster girl for an inn downtown. She came to watch the festivities today.”

“He really does have it nice, swapping women one after another. I want to be in a superior position too. His infidelity is officially approved too, right?” the knight who first mentioned Duran’s name muttered.

“What infidelity? You’re single. You have to find a bride before you can dream of cheating on her. That, and you’d better achieve as many military exploits as Prince Duran to climb the ladder of success.”

“Sh-Shut up. I was just speaking hypothetically.”

The three seemed to be friendly colleagues, as their conversation was unreserved. However, they seemed to be trained quite well, as they showed no sign of letting down their guard despite this. It was proof of their high experience.

“But there might be a way to climb the ladder without military success,” one of the knights suddenly said.

“Oh?”

“It was mentioned at the festivities today, no? Whoever can withstand one blow from Prince Duran will receive a reward. They’ll be holding it again from noon tomorrow. There are no limits to the participants, so even we could apply.”

“...Don’t joke about that. I don’t want to die yet—there’s no way I could survive a hit from Prince Duran’s enchanted sword. Not in a million years. He probably wouldn’t even hold back against us if we applied.”

The bulky knights shrunk in on themselves in fear.

“All the adventurers that participated were sent flying, after all. Those that made it out with just their armor broken were still lucky—there was one fool who tried to block Prince Duran’s downwards swing and was rendered beyond recovery.” Another knight recalled the scene with a cold smile. It seemed like the reward was being used as bait to hold an event even highly trained knights feared.

An event, huh?

Rio’s interest was piqued by that contest. The timing was a little too convenient, but Rio had never met Duran before—this development was a godsend to him.

Then there’s no need for me to risk things here.

Having decided to participate in the event, Rio quietly left the scene.

◇　◇　◇

The next day, around the same time when Christina and Flora were sent to the Paladia Forest...

Rio walked easily through the main gate to the Paladia Castle. Normally, the area was strictly off-limits to unauthorized personnel, but today the grounds were open up to the courtyard. A huge crowd of people had gathered there in excitement, blocking his view of the action.

“Whoaaa!”

Cheering could be heard from afar. Rio went up the stairs of the courtyard open for spectators, deciding to watch the event from the viewing space above.

This should do.

There were two large men wielding swords. One was clearly a rowdy adventurer, while the other was wearing a neat military uniform. Both were in their mid-twenties.

Is that man Prince Duran?

Rio focused his gaze on the man in military uniform. He had an aggressive grin and a wild air about him, but his facial features were extremely refined. As proof of that, it was clear the spectating women were all watching him with heated gazes.

The adventurer and Duran distanced themselves and faced each other in the courtyard.

“Here goes,” Duran said, charging forward to slash his sword. The adventurer was hunched over a bit, but he held his sword at the ready without moving an inch.

Suddenly, Duran slashed at the adventurer’s sword. “W-Whoa?!” The nervous adventurer was unable to stand his ground and was easily blown away.

“Oooh!!” The spectators cheered passionately. Young ladies in the crowd squealed, and Duran lowered his sword with a smug look.

“How pathetic. Prattling on about joining my squad when you’re such a weak-kneed man. Is there no one out there with some backbone?” Duran glanced down at the adventurer, who was sent flying, and shook his head in disappointment. Then he looked around at the crowd and shouted to incite them. “Well, is there?! Is there no one who can withstand one blow from me, the great Duran?! You’ll be rewarded with whatever you wish!”

The adventurers who were out to get rich quick stirred noisily.

Every adventurer yesterday and today had been beaten down; while Paladia was only a minor kingdom, the reward the first prince spoke of was attractive enough to spur them into action.

As long as they held their weapon at the ready, Duran would engage them. As long as they weren’t unlucky enough to be hit from the wrong angle, there was little chance of them meeting their demise.

Even though they had just witnessed a man be sent flying moments ago, there were several people sucking in deep breaths and summoning their courage to step forward.

Amongst them, there was one person who raised his hand immediately.

“...Oh?” Duran immediately spotted them. He easily lifted a two-handed sword up with one hand and pointed with the tip.

“The man... No, the boy over there. Come down here,” he said, nominating Rio, who had been the one to raise his hand.

“...” Rio bowed once, silently, and went down the staircase to where Duran was waiting in the center of the courtyard. The spectators opened a path for him in slight shock.

“Hey, hey...”

“That brat’s dead meat.”

“But he’s got pretty good gear on him.”

The adventurers that were too late to step forward started making their usual lively remarks.

In reality, there was quite a height difference between Duran and Rio, and their body weight was quite different too. The adventurers couldn’t foresee a still-developing boy’s body being able to withstand a hit from Duran, so it was only natural they would underestimate him. However—

“Kid. What do you want as a reward for withstanding one blow from me?” Duran asked, staring sharply at Rio as though he were watching some kind of interesting prey.

“The location of the Heavenly Lions’ captain—Lucius Orgueil,” Rio answered without hesitation.

Duran’s eyes widened faintly before he grinned. “Hmm. Very well. Draw your sword.”

“Excuse me, then.” With that preamble, Rio drew his favored blade from the sheath at his waist with a flowing gesture. A sharp but clear sound echoed, revealing the gleaming blade. Meanwhile, the spectators were holding their breath in suspense. Even the lively adventurers had quieted down, leaving the courtyard in silence.

“Interesting. An enchanted sword, huh? I’ll strike you with a blow worthy of your reward. Do not disappoint me,” Duran’s proud voice sounded clearly.

“I will do my best. Ready when you are.” Rio already had his sword braced.

“There will be no signal...”

Duran’s aura sharpened. The atmosphere was no longer that of recreation, but a real battlefield. The moment someone spectating gulped noisily—

“...” Duran kicked off from the ground without a sound. He closed the ten-meter gap between himself and Rio in a single instant, swinging his sword down from above.

“Wha...?!” The spectators lost sight of Duran as his speed surpassed what they could follow with their eyes. It was the moment they finally understood how much Duran had been holding back until now.

Meanwhile, Rio saw through Duran’s movements perfectly. Since the rule was to stop the blow, he couldn’t avoid it; instead, he held his sword ready to guard.

Zoom! The sound of the impact reverberated. Rio held his ground as he caught the blade of Duran’s enchanted sword with the blade of his own.

“You... What did you do?” Duran asked in confusion, his sword still held aloft.

“I just caught your blow,” Rio replied curiously as though he didn’t understand the question.

“Caught my blow, you say? Bah!” Duran burst into hearty laughter. “Then what was that lack of resistance I felt just now? What did I just try to cut?”

Duran corrected his question. He had definitely struck Rio’s sword with his own, but there had been no resistance.

“That’s probably because I redirected the force...”

“In a single instance? To a blow from me?” Duran often redirected the power of an opponent’s blow behind him as well, so he understood the logic. However, his eyes were wide as though he couldn’t believe it.

“Yes,” Rio nodded calmly.

“Ha. Bwahahaha!” Duran cackled.

“...” Rio stood there somewhat awkwardly.

After laughing for a while, Duran collected himself and hummed. “If it’s Lucius Orgueil’s location you want, you’ll need to wait a while. I should be able to tell you by tomorrow.”

“You know his location?”

“He’s nearby, is what I can tell you. He’s also searching for you, kid... No, Haruto Amakawa—the Galarc Kingdom’s Black Knight.”

“...”

How does he know my identity? Rio watched Duran warily.

“I simply received a message from him—one that said you would most likely visit me in search of him. I’ve hired his services out of convenience quite a few times, but we’re not allies by any means. Though I’m not a neutral party either,” Duran said suggestively, then chuckled.

“Why can’t you tell me now?” Rio asked.

“I received his message as part of an agreement—one where I was ordered not to say anything unnecessary—and I’m a man of my word. I’ve told you he’s in this country somewhere, but I actually do not know his exact location. I’m expecting him to send word today of a location to give to you. It could arrive right after this. And that’s all I can say on the subject.”

“...”

“Any objections?” Duran grinned at Rio’s silence.

“...No,” Rio said, shaking his head slowly. With his movements anticipated to this extent, it was almost certain that Lucius would have set up some kind of trap to make the first move—but in this situation, there was nothing he could do about it.

“Where are you staying?”

“I’ve rented a room at an inn in town.”

“Then I’ll have one of my knights follow you when you return. Once I’ve received word of Lucius’s location, I’ll send a messenger there. That, or I can prepare a room at the castle if you’d like to stay here?”

“...I’ll be at the inn. I won’t run or hide, either.” Rio was rather taken aback at the bold declaration of sending someone to tail him.

“What a shame. I would have liked to talk to you over drinks...” Duran sighed in disappointment.

What an odd guy.

Based on their conversation so far, Duran didn’t seem like a two-faced kind of person. He drew a line where he needed to, but it seemed like he was merely curious about Rio.

“There’s no helping it. I would risk breaking my contract with him as well. Go now.” Duran looked almost hesitant, but he sent Rio off bluntly as though to sever himself from his indecision.

“...Right.” Rio put the royal castle behind him, not feeling entirely satisfied.

◇　◇　◇

Several hours later, in the forest west of the Paladia Kingdom’s capital, a man arrived at the cabin where Christina and Flora had teleported to.

“...” The man opened the door to the silent cabin. There was no sign of anyone inside. With the lamp in his hand to light the way, he marched in. After confirming that the building was empty and that the food in the storage and sheets on the bed were gone, he concluded that someone had stopped by the cabin.

“Heh, so they chose to run. I didn’t think such sheltered princesses would have the guts.” The man—Lucius—sneered as he left the cabin, then looked around carefully at the ground outside. Two amateurs were traversing the forest—they’d definitely leave tracks of trodden vegetation.

“It’s been a few hours at most since they left the cabin. They won’t get away.”

Like a beast hunting down its prey, Lucius started treading through the quiet forest.